Honor is always worth fighting for
Valdez Is Coming is a western film directed by Edwin Sherin.
Old Mexican-American sheriff Bob Valdez has always been a haven of sanity in
a land of madmen when it came to defending law and order.
But the weapon smuggler Frank Tanner is greedy and impulsive.
When Tanner provokes a shooting that causes the death of an innocent man and Valdez asks him to financially compensate the widow,
Tanner refuses to do so and severely humiliates Valdez, who will do justice and avenge his honor, no matter what it takes.
Valdez, played by Burt Lancaster.
Gay Erin, played by Susan Clark.
Diego, played by Frank Silvera.
Frank Tanner, played by Jon Cypher.
R. L. Davis, played by Richard Jordan.
El Segundo, played by Barton Heyman.
Valdez Is Coming is a 1971 American Western film directed by Edwin Sherin and
starring Burt Lancaster, Susan Clark, Richard Jordan and Jon Cypher.
The film is based on the 1970 Elmore Leonard novel of the same name.
The film explores themes of one man army, posse, mexican
american, small town sheriff, weapons trafficking.